- I recognize a real rack kid when I see one.
- No problem.
I'm going to take revenge because he made Harry so scared.
Hello Hello!
- We're outside ... - Green Lund!
It's Halloween in there, and Hussein is with us.
Do you remember when we tested costumes?
There were a lot of people who wanted to see Hussein in his suit, so good.
- Should I try this one?
- What do you think?
What do you think?
- Yes.
Not now, but in there.
- Walk around and scare people with it.
- I don't think it's so scary.
- It's great fun, will look good when running.
Yes indeed.
It will look fun.
But, we have heard that Gröna Lund should be very scary this year.
More horror houses, more ghosts, more witches, more attractions that are open.
Here we go!
- Yes, now we drive!
- Yay!
Check out what a large spider, Harry.
Hussein went to the toilet.
- Are you peppy to see him, right?
- What you jump.
Aaah!
Hahaha!
- Should I walk around with this one?
- Absolutely!
It is absolutely amazing.
Wait, I have to film.
It's so fun!
LOL!
- Run!
- There is no danger, there is no danger.
He is just an ordinary person with makeup, loose teeth and red lentils that make his eyes red.
How quiet you are.
Are you not happy?
I who want happy people here at my circus.
I recognize a real rack kid when I see one.
- Mom, maybe you should check behind you.
- Oh!
Come, Alma.
Did it fall asleep?
- Do you want to shake hands with it?
- No.
- May I do it?
- Yes.